# ALESSANDRO PEPE

#### **Profile**

An independent, organized, and highly motivated professional. Versatile and versed in fields such as advertising, marketing, journalism, communications, and SEO optimization. A skilled problem-solver with experience in B2B copy, B2C copy, Google meta descriptions, radio ads, social media ads, blogging, and email sales. Lifetime of technology knowledge.

## **Experience**

## Freelance Copywriter

Self Employed, June 2015 - Present

Wrote copy in many formats and lengths. Industries in health, higher education, and luxury goods. Companies included Synergixx, Comcast, and Invisalign.

#### Copywriter

Burlington Stores, August 2016 - December 2016
Wrote engaging copy for fashion products of all types and styles. Worked with open ended SEO guidelines, exceeded quota by 100%. Devised meta tags for Google for traffic incentive to the website.

## Supplemental Experience

#### **Graduate Advisor**

Rutgers University, June 2015 - June 2016

Trained incoming and current students in class selection procedures. Practiced face to face sales of classes upon students in need of credits. Consulted for advising deans on potential class tracks for students.

#### Team Member

Target, August 2011 - December 2015

Worked three in-depth and titled positions concurrently, every day. Learned vital time-management and resource allocation techniques. Trained fellow team members on best practices and organization processes.

#### **Education**

Master of Arts in English Rutgers University, 2017

Bachelor of Arts in English Rutgers University, 2015

#### Who I Am

A dreamer, a writer, and a thinker. An avid lover of literature was kindled at an early age, whose love of language was fanned from a spark into a flame through tales of fantasy and intrigue, and tempered throughout college and graduate school into a master of the written word.

## Qualifications



Aggregate experience



Process oriented; sterling results



Eagle-eyed, detail-oriented



Technologically inclined



Team player



Best under pressure

856-278-9610 apepe1024@gmail.com

## Portfolio:

alessandropepe.org